Mr. Chu
is indeed the top scholar in the capital.
He not only restored the original work
but also added his own charm.
Can you see anything unusual
about this painting
of the princess's marriage alliance?
It seems
to use the same canvas
as the painting your mother left behind.
When I repainted
the Nirvana of the Phoenix,
I couldn't find
the exact same canvas,
so I had to use rice paper instead.
This kind of canvas is not common,
and the material is very special.
So I remember it.
What else besides that?
I can't tell anything else.
I was so foolish.
Even I can tell
that the evidence of treason
was forged by Xue Shiyan.
How could he not see it?
He did it on purpose.
It is just a painting.
If you are interested, General,
let us admire it together.
Why is
this empty?
You old scoundrel,
you ordered me to forge
the Iron Cavalry Map,
attempting to use me
to pass military secrets in public.
I painted it with a special ink
that fades in three days.
Don't even think about making me
take the fall for your treason.
Everyone, bear witness.
He clearly swapped my painting.
You think you can frame me
with a blank canvas?
You think I don't know
the secret of this canvas?
My ink will fade,
but yours will not.
I ask you all to be the judge.
Xue Shiyan gave this painting to me.
Whatever message it holds
will be revealed by fire.
Cui Hu!
General!
Ning Yuanci,
what are you doing?
The Northern spies
are hiding among the guests today.
Arrest them all!
Xue Shiyan,
the evidence of your treason
is conclusive.
Take him away too!
Ning Yuanci,
you are too impatient.
The truth has not yet been fully revealed.
Everyone, please look.
This is
Ning Yuanci's personal seal.
How could this be?
Ning Yuanci!
We were all deceived by him.
Chu Qingyun is highly skilled in painting.
Ning Yuanci wanted to use him
to pass on the intel.
And the private seal
in the bottom right corner
proves that
Ning Yuanci,
who holds the city defense map,
is the real traitor
and deserves to die.
Ning Yuanci, watch out!
You rebellious daughter,
you don't even recognize your own father!
Come with me.
I'm not leaving.
Let me go!
Then don't blame me for being ruthless.
Men,
tie her up!
Keying,
Chu Qingjun,
I was too smart for my own good.
I thought
I could protect you.
Don't speak.
Ning Yuanci,
help!
Keying, watch out!
Surrender now,
or she dies.
No,
don't do anything stupid.
Let her go.
Ying'er!
Kill Ning Yuanci,
and I'll let your sister go.
Leave me alone!
Ning Yuanci,
take her away!
Are you protecting Ning Yuanci
or your sister?
Make a choice.
General,
I will cover you.
Retreat!
Are you coming with us or not?
Leave, now!
General!
Alright.
Cui Hu, hear my command.
Lead the army
to reclaim the Northern Frontier.
Keying,
I will make this choice for you.
Take me instead.
Let them both go.
No.
Alright.
A life for a life.
No!
Ning Yuanci,
do not go.
General!
Go!
You are as foolish
as your father.
No!
Ning Yuanci, go.
Go!
Ning Yuanci!
Ning Yuanci,
I...
As long as I die,
you can survive.
As long as you survive,
you can go back to
your own world.
I'm not going back.
I'm not going back, okay?
I
can't
walk
with you
to the end of the story.
My ending
just
ends right
here.
No.
Ning Yuanci!
Xuyu,
come out!
I don't want an ending like this.
Xue Keying,
are you sure you want to start over?
Ning Yuanci is obviously
the second male lead.
How could he
die so easily?
Who's talking?
You said it yourself.
I have five chances to role-play.
Restarting with Ning Yuanci last time
and changing the method
was completely wrong.
I want to restart the plot.
I want to do it again.
Your plot mission
hasn't failed.
Xue Ruowan is still alive.
You can still continue acting.
If you want the plot to restart now,
the female lead Xue Ruowan
must die.
What?
Don't worry.
After Xue Ruowan dies,
the story timeline will restart.
All past events
will be wiped clean.
All characters
will come back to life.
There's only one chance left.
Trying again doesn't guarantee success.
You're only one step away
from the finale now.
Think carefully before making a decision.
Why force me
to make such a decision?
Ying'er!
Is what he said true?
Will everyone really come back to life
if I die?
If so,
I'm willing to do it.
You always say
I'm the heroine of some story,
and that our lives
are tied together.
You've always saved me before.
This time,
let me do it.
No!
Besides, I believe
you'll keep me safe,
won't you?
Silly girl.
Be brave.
Sister!
No!
These are
a maid's clothes.
I've become Lan again.
This is Jinming Pool.
The timeline has returned
to the night of the engagement banquet.
She dances so well.
Wonderful.
It's still Xue Keying's face.
So wonderful.
Young Master Chu is so handsome.
Chu Qingyun!
Miss, you are...
It is me,
Xue Keying,
the Second Miss
of the Duke of Ying's Mansion,
Xue Ruowan's younger sister.
As far as I know,
the Duke of Ying has only one daughter
named Xue Ruowan.
I have never heard of
her having a younger sister.